An unlikely friendship. An impossible mission.
Project Hail Mary is a science fiction, adventure,
mystery film directed by Phil Lord.
Astronaut Ryland Grace awakens on a spacecraft with
no memory of himself or his mission.
He slowly deduces he is the sole survivor of a crew sent to the Tau Ceti solar
system in search of a solution to a catastrophic event on Earth.
In his search for answers, Grace must rely on his vast array of scientific knowledge,
sheer ingenuity, and human will – but he may not have to search alone.
Ryland Grace, played by Ryan Gosling.
Eva Stratt, played by Sandra Hüller.
Martin DuBois, played by Lionel Boyce.
Yáo Li-Jie, played by Ken Leung.
Olesya Ilyukhina, played by Milana Vayntrub.
Annie Shapiro, played by Liz Kingsman.
Project Hail Mary is an upcoming American science fiction adventure film produced and directed by Phil Lord
and Christopher Miller, and written by Drew Goddard, based on the 2021 novel by Andy Weir.
It stars Ryan Gosling (who is also a producer), Sandra Hüller,
Lionel Boyce, Ken Leung, and Milana Vayntrub.
The film follows a man who awakens on an interstellar
spacecraft with no memory of how he came to be there.
Project Hail Mary is scheduled to be released in the United
States by Amazon MGM Studios on March 20, 2026.
The film explores themes of based on novel or book,
space, alien friendship, near future.
The tone is thought_provoking and mind_bending.